The smell in the shop just now
was exactly that.
Master.
Goodness.
He actually went straight into Fan Restaurant.
This matter is of great importance.
Follow me to a safe place first.
This piece
is Ambush from Ten Sides.
My sister is using the zither to warn me.
This area
has been surrounded by Imperial City Department spies.
This one
is 'Deep in the Zen Quarters'.
This way, please.
Please wait here for a moment.
Sister.
You've worked hard.
This time,
I'm afraid I've really dragged you into this.
Between us,
there's no need to talk about being a burden.
It's just,
what exactly happened?
Overnight,
you became wanted all over the city.
An open attack is easy to dodge,
but a hidden arrow is hard to guard against.
Especially...
or an arrow in the back from an insider.
Three honored guests,
food has been prepared in the side hall.
Please enjoy.
Let's go, old man.
Brother Chaijiu.
I don't eat.
I don't eat cooked food.
I want to eat it raw.
Brother Chaijiu,
you'd better get used to it slowly.
To the good days under the bright sun,
we have to return.
My poor days in that little mud hut
weren't so bad either.
Then why did you target Lord Chu
last night?
It wasn't really targeting.
I just felt
that someone who was once powerful
could fall into the dust the next.
I was just a little curious.
Who hasn't had a time of being down and out?
The dignified Huo Sanlang in the market back then
now acting so loyal and submissive to his master.
More real than my dog brother.
Say that again if you dare.
Don't be rash, old man.
Old man.
But, old man,
how did you end up becoming
her subordinate?
Maybe my strange fire evasion technique
was somewhat useful.
Didn't it
scare off
someone showing their animalistic side?
Brother Chaijiu,
don't.
Brother Chaijiu, don't be mad.
Don't be mad.
Old man.
She doesn't seem that great.
Why did you agree to it?
From the first time I saw Lord Chu,
I felt she was my daughter,
because she and my late wife
look almost exactly the same.
If my daughter hadn't died,
she'd be about her age.
I feel like Lord Chu
is the person I'm looking for.
That's how it happened.
I didn't expect Feng Xiu to frame me.
Sister.
This trouble of yours
is probably because of your insistence on catching the assassin.
To protect His Majesty's safety.
It is my duty at the Ice Bureau.
Why would he frame me at a time like this?
Zhou You's actions earlier didn't seem like he wanted to harm you,
but rather to save you.
Save me?
What do you mean?
He is the Deputy Director of the Palace Domestic Service.
If he wanted to harm you,
he has plenty of ways.
Why would he need
to get himself involved?
That's the first point.
And the second?
If Zhou You wanted to save you,
he didn't need to use such obscure methods.
So I boldly guess
that the person behind the scenes
must be someone even Zhou You dare not provoke.
Someone Zhou You dare not provoke,
and who can also command the Imperial City Division?
Could it be
the Chief Eunuch Liang Shicheng?
It can only be him.
My Chu family has merit in supporting the Emperor
and has received imperial grace.
Why would he harm me like this?
Don't worry, sister.
If we can get Zhou You's help now,
there might still be a turning point.
Zhou You and I have no ties.
Why would he take such a great risk to help me?
Not necessarily.
I
heard a rumor the other day
that Liang Shicheng
is deeply colluding with the princes,
which has displeased the Emperor.
In my opinion,
his favor
is probably not as it used to be.
How can we overcome this ordeal?
In the end,
you are the cause of this.
As for catching the assassins,
if you fail to catch them,
and something happens to the Emperor
on the day of the Lantern Festival,
no matter how good the solution is,
you won't be able to escape punishment.
Therefore,
I should catch the assassins first
and ensure the Emperor's safety on the night of the Lantern Festival.
Sister.
Is there no other way
to find the thieves?
There is a way.
But come to think of it,
he will also have concerns.
Even if we find him.
I have no military power or troops right now.
What's the use of finding the thieves?
I don't know.
Who has a solution?
It's the idler I mentioned during the day,
Meng Qian.
Then there is always a way out.
What do you mean, sister?
Is that Meng Qian
one of the three who just entered the manor?
Lord Chu.
Young man,
you
have been staring at me.
Is there something wrong
with my face?
Keep looking,
and I'll dig your eyes out.
My lady,
are you feeling unwell?
Why do you say that?
I have a younger sister
who has been ill since childhood.
Her posture
is very similar to yours.
I see.
Pardon my intrusion.
It's fine.
You could tell at a glance
that I was unwell.
It shows
you know your sister's condition well.
You are a good brother.
Could my sister-in-law and sister be in this manor?
What does it matter if they are or not?
I told you,
they are safe.
As long as you do that job,
I naturally won't treat them badly.
What?
You don't believe what I said?
Even if you knew where they are,
what could you do?
If you can't catch the Liangshan assassins
and get the medicine,
even if you see them.
We can't do anything anyway.
We'd better figure out a way quickly.
What you said makes sense, sir.
Young man.
This sister of mine,
though hot-tempered,
always keeps her promises and does what she says.
If she says she won't mistreat your sister-in-law and younger sister,
then she definitely won't.
You can rest assured.
You too, sister.
Since everyone is sincere about doing this,
why don't we talk it over nicely?
Alright.
Let's get down to business first.
Hurry!
Keep up!
Surround them!